[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 0, "question": "Is this the U.S. military's dirty secret?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1, "answer": "Nobody wants to say that there's been a rape in their command.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["fiscal year 2009"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Sexual Assault Prevention Response Office", "DOD"]}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CD", ",", "IN", "CD", ":", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "How many cases are we seeing per year and is it getting worse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "In the last report by the Sexual Assault Prevention Response Office in fiscal year 2009, over 3,000 -- 3,230 sexual assaults were reported throughout DOD, all the four branches.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Berk Peel LLC"], "LOCATION": ["Washington", "D.C."]}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Why have you taken that step and do you think you can be successful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Well, the case has been brought by Berk Peel LLC, a law firm in Washington, D.C. and we're -- sort of spokesman and consultant for the suit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "What was happening to you before you got raped?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Well, it is a very hyper masculine culture and I did a predominantly male job.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "What did you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "My first reaction was I just want to go home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2005"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Department of Defense"]}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "So Myla, in essence, you end up getting sexually abused and raped and you then get thrown out of the military, and this is after nine years of great service to your country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "VBG", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Right, I was administratively discharged and I spent five years after my discharge fighting with the Department of Defense to get my record corrected and five years after my discharge in 2005 I was finally awarded a medical retirement.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Myla"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Is that one of the main reasons that you didn't pursue this and didn't report it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "It was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Fort Leonard Wood", "Missouri"]}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "And Rebekah, you actually went to one of the army chaplains who gave you some extraordinary advice, didn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Yes, about a year later, I had gotten out of the army and moved to Fort Leonard Wood, Missouri, and I ran into the guy that raped me and went into a little bit of shock and requested to speak to a sexual assault response coordinator or to a chaplain.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rebekah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Which is really unacceptable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Completely, and it's even worse in job fields that tend to be male dominated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Army"]}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "And what would you say, Myla?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "I would say that it is very much a command accountability issue and institutionally the military is sexist but most of the workplaces that I worked in when I was in the Army, the leadership had zero tolerance for any sexual harassment so in the workplaces in which the command did not support that atmosphere I didn't have any problems.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Myla"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Or is that an unfair labeling really of the situation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, I think sexism is allowed to exist generally in the military but the larger problem with sexual abuse in the military is there's no institutional accountability.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "What happened when this all became a public matter for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Well, at the time that I was approached by the investigator to give a statement, I already knew at that time that giving a statement would end my career in CID.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Yes, but did everybody ostracize you or were there any Good Samaritan types who came forward to offer you protection?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Well, several of my good friends really stood by me throughout this ordeal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Did you have the same experience as Myla?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "I did not, and I did not because I chose to use a restricted reporting option and that's exactly why I chose to use that option because I knew if I started an investigation that there would be the ostracism -- the criticism.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Myla, the option that Rebekah is talking about, what is that exactly and why didn't you take it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "The restricted reporting option is an option in which a victim can report the crime to only certain individuals including medical personnel and the necessary evidence will be collected and then the victim can maintain some level of confidentiality, but they are actually ordered not to talk to anybody else about it, not even friends.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rebekah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "What is the situation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Well, of course, I mean there are lots of positives.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Did you see any abuse when you were serving?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "And do you remain proud of your service in the military?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "I actually don't regret joining the military at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Rebekah, how about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "RP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I don't regret it, but I don't think that I would do it again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "What happens?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Well, we'll se what happens with the lawsuit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "What would your message be to any young woman watching this who has been interested in pursuing a career in the military, but is now horrified at what she's hearing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "I would encourage any young woman or man to follow his or her dreams and to join the military if that's what they want to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Second?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "-- \"America's Got Talent\" obviously.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "How do you feel now it's all out in the open?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "You know, I feel relief.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "How old were you at the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "I was five years old.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Then what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Then he would touch me inappropriately and I knew it was inappropriate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Even at the age of five?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Even at the age -- I just felt uncomfortable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Classic pedophile behavior, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "At the time, did you tell your mother or your stepfather anything about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "I couldn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "What was your mother's reaction, in particular, when you said to her that you had also been through this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "I -- what I remember -- because it's such a foggy memory since I was just five years old, I just remember them in shock and then the next thing I remember is I'm testifying against him in court at age six.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "ORGAN: Can you remember much of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "I can just remember the feeling I felt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "That she left you with this guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Sometimes I feel like both of them feel guilty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "What's been the impact to you psychologically, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "I think a lot, growing up with no self-esteem, no confidence, getting into abusive relationships in high school with men, not knowing my boundaries, feeling like I always need to please and have no self-respect for who I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "What kind of child were you before that happened, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Quiet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Why did you do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Because I was scared to be alone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "He keeps spinning you the same old story, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "When -- you know when he came back and he was upset, I felt like I couldn't leave.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "What made you finally do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "URKE: My dancing, just being called from New York, a great -- a great opportunity for me here happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "And never looked back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Never looked back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "How are you now, do you think, psychologically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "I think I'm still healing and I'm a work in progress, for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Do you have bad days, when you just lose it because of all that's happened to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Not so much meltdowns.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Do you -- do you trust men?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "I have a hard time trusting men.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "But I can imagine every one that comes up to you, particularly if you're famous, it's even more difficult to get any kind of trust going, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "NN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "-- and people poking fun at you?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Yes, I mean put -- putting yourself -- I was put on blast for my weight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "So when you look at yourself there, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "No, I don't think I'm fat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "I mean, this is dangerous stuff, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "It is dangerous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "What would you say to the old man who took away your innocence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "I would say thank God I testified against you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]